You can't escape a mother's love.
Run is a thriller, horror, drama film directed by Aneesh Chaganty.
Chloe, a teenager who is confined to a wheelchair, is
homeschooled by her mother, Diane.
Chloe soon becomes suspicious of her mother and begins to
suspect that she may be harboring a dark secret.
Mother / Diane, played by Sarah Paulson.
Daughter / Chloe, played by Kiera Allen.
Mailman, played by Pat Healy.
Nurse, played by Sara Sohn.
Doctor, played by Erik Athavale.
Meeting Leader, played by BJ Harrison.
Run (referred to on-screen as Run.) is a 2020 American psychological horror thriller
film directed by Aneesh Chaganty, and written by Chaganty and Sev Ohanian.
The film stars Kiera Allen as disabled teenager Chloe Sherman, who begins to suspect that her
mother, Diane (Sarah Paulson), has been keeping a dark secret about her upbringing.
The film has connections to other films by Chaganty and Ohanian and is the
second installment in the filmmaking duo's Searching film series.
Run was released in the United States via streaming on November 20, 2020, on Hulu, and was released in other
territories both theatrically and through streaming by Lionsgate International and by Netflix on April 2, 2021.
The film received generally positive reviews from critics and became
Hulu's most successful original film upon its release.
The film explores themes of small town, wheelchair user   ,
homeschooling, single mother, washington state.
The tone is dark and emotional and intense.